Tufts Traveler UP247
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Traveler
2005 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Media Advocacy Board
UP247
0.5 Linear Feet
1 Web sites
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Tufts Traveler and Web crawls.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Tufts Traveler, Tufts' student-produced travel magazine, and web crawls documenting its web presence. It publishes full-color magazines, featuring student generated content including articles, reviews, and photographs. It is a magazine for students traveling and studying abroad.
- Tufts Traveler, 2005 -- 2015; UP247.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Tufts Traveler, Tufts' student-produced travel magazine. It publishes full-color magazines, featuring student generated content including articles, reviews, and photographs. It is a magazine for students traveling and studying abroad.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Traveler, Fall, 2005; UP247.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    A magazine for students traveling and studying abroad.
  - Tufts Traveler, Brazil, Fall, 2006; UP247.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    Volume
    III
  - Tufts Traveler, Italy, Winter, 2006; UP247.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    IV
  - Tufts Traveler, Sub-Saharan Africa, Spring, 2007; UP247.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    V
  - Tufts Traveler, Greece, Spring, 2007; UP247.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    Volume, issue
    II, VI
  - Tufts Traveler India, Fall, 2007; UP247.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler Holiday Issue, Fall, 2007; UP247.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, The Caribbean, Spring, 2008; UP247.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Boston, Fall, 2008; UP247.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, China, Fall, 2008; UP247.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, France, Spring, 2009; UP247.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Israel, Spring, 2009; UP247.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Greece, Fall, 2009; UP247.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, United Kingdom and Ireland, Spring, 2010; UP247.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Boston and Her Sister Cities, Spring, 2010; UP247.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Scandinavia, Fall, 2010; UP247.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Road Trips, Winter, 2011; UP247.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Latin America, Spring, 2011; UP247.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Australia and New Zealand, Fall, 2011; UP247.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Mountains, Fall, 2011; UP247.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Italy, Spring, 2011; UP247.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Goodnight, Spring, 2012; UP247.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, Going Native, Fall, 2013; UP247.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, In Transit, Spring, 2014; UP247.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Traveler, The Great Perhaps, Fall, 2015; UP247.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2020; UP247.002; 1 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the Tufts Traveler Magazine website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Tufts Traveler Magazine, 2015 -- 2020; UP247.002.00001; Media Advocacy Board
    General
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.